Okay, so let's get started on actually solving this problem. We've
好 我们来开始实际解决这个问题
got to remember that the first step in our procedure is
我们要记得 我们程序的第一步是
to extract the complete list of carriers and the complete list
从一个示例页面提取承运人的完整列表
of airports from one example page. So, what I've done here
和机场的完整列表 所以 我在这里做的是
is downloaded this page and I'm simply going to parse this
下载本页面 然后我要开始解析该页面
page in order to pull out both these lists. So let's
以便取得这两张列表
take a look at some code. Now, what I like to
让我们来看一些代码 我用来解析 HTML 的是
use for parsing HTML is BeautifulSoup.
BeautifulSoup
In particular, we're using BeautifulSoup four.
更具体地说 是 BeautifulSoup 4
You can download and install BeautifulSoup on your own machine
有很多文件包管理软件 大家可以任选其一来下载 BeautifulSoup
using any one of a number of different package managers.
并将其安装到本地
I like to use PIP. If you don't already have
我个人喜欢用 PIP 如果你还没有安装 BeautifulSoup
BeautifulSoup installed, just Google for
可以用 Google 搜索安装说明
installation instructions. Now, what BeautifulSoup gives
BeautifulSoup 能让我们
us the ability to do is parse the document tree,
解析文档树
the HTML document tree in this case. And, it's similar to
就本例来说 是解析 HTML 文档设树
elementary for parsing XML. Okay. So let me walk you
这与解析 XML 的基本方法类似 好 我来向大家展示
through how this code works. So what I've done is I've
该代码是如何工作的 我所做的是
set this up so that it's the options function
完成了对其的配置 以便由选项功能
that does the bulk of the work. I'm calling
来进行大部分的工作 我要调用选项
options and note that what I'm calling it with
注意 我用来调用的是
is this soup value. And soup is what I
soup 值 而 soup 则是
get in response to having called beautiful soup on
我在本地文件调用 beautiful soup 后 作为响应而得到的
the local file that is a saved copy Of
该本地文件是这份文件的一个保存副本
this one. In addition, I'm passing this string CarrierList.
另外 我要传递这个字符串 CarrierList
Now what BeautifulSoup passed me back was the top level
BeautifulSoup 传递给我的是
element for this particular HTML document. And then what
这份 HTML 文档的顶级元素 然后我能做的是
I can do is I can use the find method
使用这里的 查找 方法
here. The meaning of this is find me the
其意思是帮我查找到
the first descendant element in this document tree where the
文档树中的第一个后代元素
ID attribute for the element is CarrierList. Okay? So
在该文档树上 元素的 ID 属性为 CarrierList 对吗？
let's go look at the HTML, and see why we
那我们来研究这个 HTML 知道我们
wrote it that way. Okay? Again, I can get
为何要以这种方式编写它吗？这一次
to the HTML by using the Inspect Element feature of
我还是可以使用 Google Chrome 的检查元素功能来找到该 HTML
Google Chrome. Okay. So here's the CarrierList, and note that the ID attribute
这是 CarrierList 注意 该元素的 ID 属性是
for this particular element here is CarrierList.
CarrierList
Okay, so CarrierList, then, will have the HTML element that we
是 CarrierList 然后 我们将刚才研究的 HTML 元素作为其值
just looked at as its value. Then what I'm going to do is call Find all
然后 针对 CarrierList 我要调用 查找所有
on CarrierList. Find all does something very similar
查找所有与查找非常相似
to what find does. It finds the descendants
它会找出选项标签
that are option tags or option elements. Now unlike
或选项元素等后代 不过与查找不同的是
find, find all will actually find all of the
查找所有实际会找到所有句子
sentence instead of just the first one. Okay, so
而并非只是第一个
here what's going to happen is I'll just iterate through them
好 这里将会发生的情况是 我将只能循环访问它们
then, and I'm going to just build up a list
而我只能构建一个所有值的列表
of all of the values. Now what I'm actually doing
这里我实际做的是
here Is finding each one of these in turn
按顺序找到它们中的每一个
and I'm pulling out the value of their value attribute.
并且将拉取其值属性的值
Because, it's this value that I need to pass in any subsequent http
因此 这是我在随后任何有关（比如说）
requests for data having to do with, say, AirTran or Alaska airlines. So
AirTran 航空或阿拉斯加航空公司的 http 数据请求中需要传递的值
that's how we get the carrier data we need. I use a very similar
这就是如何获得我们需要的承运人的方法 我采用的是
process, in fact it's an identical process,
一种非常类似的过程 事实上 就是与获取航空公司完整列表
for getting the full list of airports.
相同的过程